<about>
	We are three college students who enjoy making web sites.
	We feel energized by the unique challenges presented by
	every site we get the chance to build.  We love the process.
	[break]
	We want to do things differently.  We want to make web sites
	like no one else makes.  We want to do things that have
	never been done before.
	[break]
	We never stop exploring possibilities and learning new
	things.
</about>

<contact>
	<email>info@humortree.com</email>
	<telephone>(903) 663 4491</telephone>
	<fax>(903) 663 4591</fax>
	<address>
		122 Oak Isle Drive
		Longview, TX 75605
	</address>
</contact>

<process>
	<step number="1">
		Initial meeting.  At this point we do our best to
		get to know you and your business, so that we can try
		to help you figure out exactly where a web site would
		help you out.  If we feel that you wouldn't gain anything
		from a web presence, we will let you know.<br /><br />
	</step>
	<step number="2">
		Based on the initial meeting, we create a timeline
		that maps out the stages of development that are
		required to produce your web site.  We estimate how
		long we expect each stage to take, and how much
		we charge for each stage.  We then return this timeline
		to you, for you to review.<br /><br />
	</step>
	<step number="3">
		Once we agree on a timeline, we present you with a
		consulting agreement to sign.  We offer two methods
		of payment at the moment, and at this point you will
		pick which method you would prefer to use to pay us.
		Once the initial payment has been made, we start the
		development of your site.<br /><br />
	</step>
	<step number="4">
		Once the development has started, we follow the timeline.  Generally,
		we present you with an initial design that we feel
		meets the goals you've set for your site.  You are
		welcome to make suggestions for improvements, or to
		request a new design.  Once a design is chosen, we
		begin to code the site.  We will give you a web
		address where you can check our progress on the site,
		and make sure that you are comfortable with it.  Once
		the site is completely finished and thoroughly tested,
		we present it to you on your choice of mediums: floppy
		disk, CD, or Zip disk.  Or, we can upload it straight
		to your server.<br /><br />
	</step>
	<step number="5">
		In the months that follow, we check with you to make
		sure that everything is running smoothly, and to see
		if there are any changes that need to be made.  We
		want you to be completely satisfied.
	</step>
</process>

<skills>
	<languages>
	
	</languages>
</skills>